Guide to the Rice University Historic Clothing collection, 1916-2017 UA 392
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas
- Series IX: T-shirts
  - Student Life T-shirts
    - Electrical Engineering t-shirt, n.d. (Box 57)
    - Engineering t-shirt, n.d. (Box 57)
    - "Motel Weiss" t-shirt, n.d. (Box 57)
    - Princeton Review t-shirt "We Score More", n.d. (Box 57)
    - "Rice Owls Give Back", n.d. (Box 57)
    - "Rice SPS: A Dodds-fearing society", n.d. (Box 57)
    - "Rice Study Abroad", n.d. (Box 57)
    - Richard E. Smalley Institute for Nanoscale science and technology at Rice University (Box 57)
    - "Tunnel Naked" t-shirt with nude man in basement (on front) and map of steam pipes on campus (on back) (Box 57)
    - "Willy's Pub", n.d. (Box 57)
      Immediate Source of Acquisition
      Materials donated by Walter Underwood in 2019.
  - Rice Historical T-shirts
    - Willy "Jack" statue turned around commemoration t-shirt, 1988 (Box 57)
    - "Twenty-five years of Baker Shakespeare" t-shirt, 1995 (Box 57)
    - 20 year commemorative Willy statue reversal t-shirt (blue), 2008 (Box 57)
    - 20 year commemorative Willy statue reversal t-shirt (white), 2008 (Box 57)
    - "Fondren Library 60 years of Service (1949-2009)" commemorative t-shirt (Box 57)
    - The Centennial Campaign t-shirt, 2012 (Box 57)
    - Curl and Smalley Nobel Prize t-shirt (Box 57)
    - "Dr. Bill: The Man. The Legend." t-shirt (Dr. Bill Wilson) (Box 57)
    - "The Trust, Quadrangle Films" (Box 57)
  - Alumni/Faculty T-shirts
    - Rice Alumni at National Instruments, n.d. (Box 58)
    - Fondren Library polo shirt (Box 58)
    - Rice Student Center employee collared shirt, n.d. (Box 58)
    - "Owlmaha: Summer home of Rice Alumni" t-shirt, n.d. (Box 58)
    - Class T-shirts
      - "Last Class from the Rice Institute" t-shirt, 1960 (Box 58)
      - Tie-dyed t-shirt Rice Class of 1972 (Box 58)
      - Blue t-shirt Rice Class of 2005 (Box 58)
      - Rice Alumni Class of 2006 t-shirt (Box 58)
      - Rice Alumni Class of 2008 t-shirt (Box 58)
  - Generic Rice T-shirts
    - Baseball jersey style t-shirt, 2003 (Box 58)
    - Blue t-shirt "I've Taken the Tour" with owl logo, for virtual campus tours online, ca. 2008 (Box 58)
    - Blue t-shirt "Rice -- Unconventional Wisdom", 2010 (Box 58)
    - Gray Rice University Owls t-shirt, n.d. (Box 58)
    - Blue t-shirt with "Rice" and owl logo (Box 58)
    - White t-shirt with blue script "RICE", n.d. (Box 58)
    - Tan t-shirt "Rice University" script on front, W.M. Rice portrait on back, n.d. (Box 58)
    - Gray Rice long-sleeved shirt, n.d. (Box 58)
    - "First Unbelievable Celebration of Knee-deep Water and Disaster Spectacular" t-shirt, 1970s (Box 58)
- Series X: Accessories
  - Allie May Autry [Kelley] May Fete crown, May, 1925 (Box 59)
  - Allie May Autry's May Fete Train, 1925 (Box 60)
  - Red suspenders and bow tie belonging to Roy Nolen '60, 1960 (Box 61)
  - Necktie made for Rice University by John Outram for opening of Duncan Hall – donated by Nancy Booth, October 13, 2001 (Box 61)
  - Wiess College necktie (black with gold stripes) (Box 61)
  - John Plapp "Plapp tie" hand painted necktie (Box 61)
  - Red suspenders and bow tie belonging to Ed Jennngs (Class of 1948) (Box 61)
- Series XI: Miscellaneous Clothing
  - Jumpsuit worn by Hamilton Joseph Nelson, Engineering Student, 1943 (Box 62)
  - Blue Striped Knit Shirt (Box 62)
  - 1 pair white pants with pink stripes owned by Wendell Ley (Box 62)
  - Men's suit made from Autry Court curtain in royal blue velvet (commissioned by Athletic Director Chris del Conte) (Oversize Hanging Clothes Storage)
  - Rice Letter Sweater for Tennis earned by Edwin Ford Beckenbach, 1928 (Box 63)
  - White Rice Sweater with blue "R" owned by Edwin Jennings (Box 63)
  - Blue "Rice" Sweater with grey stripe (acrylic) (Box 63)